Heat. Heat.
by
14 international
I'm
just like congratulations to all of the
honories this evening.
I
have not here this evening. So I'm going
to read his introduction and
induction
close. I wish I could be with you all
tonight. Thank you for me.
I want to thank the handsome family for
their commitment and choosing
outstanding candidates each
year. Congratulations on 15
years. Also, congratulations to all the
winners this year.
The winners are not chosen because they
are better, but because they have made
themselves better for all of
us. I have been privileged to know many
years throughout the United States.
Frank stands out by far as one of the
best because of what he
accomplish. I will not list them all.
Many things done are still kids in this
city. The Cleveland for
education, Rocky
Mort, the West Shore
way neighborhood
redevelopment. What is also wonderful is
that he did honesty and integrity and
also as an advocate for people of all
colors.
It is what it is. What his action says
is we will not accept what it is. We are
going to change it.
Thank you for making Cleveland a
better everyone in this room that is
part of the international community
first of all know what
happened the international community
can't see all the country want you to
open up a place. We want a welcoming
center. We want to use the old time
here. But he did say I don't want a
welcoming city in city hall because at
some point city I want community and
that's where Cleveland was born out of
you all remember Cleveland was born out
of that
um idea to help create this.
Mayor Jackson has illustrated as the 56
mayor. He's the 56 mayor of the
city with his actions with his
commitments to everything that he has
done. He was accountable to what he
told. He's the same person. You can go
back and pull all of his dresses. He
told you everything he was going to do
before he told
you. He never wavered. He never changed
at the heart of everything that he
believed in. He believed in the people
of the city of
[Applause]
people stood up. They were they deserve
to have
as always say they only ask people what
they deserve to have as a president of
the city of Cleveland. And so when you
think about the international community
and you just where we are in history
today, everyone in this room plays a
role to the leadership and the integrity
that may gain. We are who we are. We are
one another. There's no difference
between us. We're different shades of
excellence. And Jackson was so bad in
his administration. I told you if he got
out
here, but you deserve you have led. You
have fought. You are
exempt. We as
[Music]
I'm
sorry.
Heat. Heat.
and
this
[Music]
also one of the
best
deal and it didn't
matter the
con of whatever it was even the time we
organized trips overseas various
countries that we went to was done by
international community. And so I wanted
to thank them for the work today because
Cleveland is what it is
today because of us as individuals but
because of groups and generations that
have gone before us that have made us
who we are today.
just one
person. Uh my father is is an African
American black and uh
he is from his side of the family. We've
been traced for generations in this
country for generations.
on my mother's side. My grandfather, her
father was born
again
19. So my mother was the first
generation born here in which the
second born, born in the United States,
which makes me the second generation.
I mention that to say that Cleveland is
a
place where
everybody as we said earlier can be who
they want to be. They can accomplish
what they want to accomplish. And
Cleveland is a
place generations of people who have
sacrificed and who have done things that
we may not remember as as groups but as
individuals and as families. Heat. Heat.
Heat.
[Music]
Heat up here.